I never did I expect to hear that I had
a lump in my breast and my lymph nodes I
mean two lungs that's that's insane
right who would have thought to be
honest you know until up until this
happened to me I just found insurance so
complicated and the moment I hear
insurance is like numbers and death and
taxes and all these you know like it was
just all a part of that thing that you
don't want to think about at the moment
because you're living life what I love
about FWD is that it's not just about
insurance it's not just about money
they're actually put in care there and
they really want to change the way
people think about insurance so we're
making it real for them because that's
what if the we do you want to show you
that it is real it is life and you can
never be too prepared
[Music]